A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.32 (A2006) FA483
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2006.029: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2005; AC.2006.029; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3779-R3781.; 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3779-R3781.
  - Global Inclusion (GI), AC.2006.029.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2000 GI 099 - GREEN WORLD FOUNDATION (THAILAND) - WORKSHOP ON RIVER CARE IN THE MEKONG REGION, 2000-2004 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 101 - NEPAL WATER CONSERVATION FOUNDATION - MEETING ON WATER RESOURCES, HUMAN RIGHTS AND GOVERNANCE, 2000-2002 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 103 - TAY NGUYEN UNIVERSITY (VIETNAM) - WORKSHOP ON WATER MANAGEMENT, 2000-2005 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 106 - WATER POLICY INTERNATIONAL (ENGLAND) - WORKSHOP ON DEVELOPMENT IN THE NILE BASIN, 2000-2002 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 108 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - TRANSPARENCY AND CIVIL SOCIETY PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 112 - CENTER FOR INTERNATIONAL ENVIRONMENTAL LAW - TRADE AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT, 2000-2002 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 114 - UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME - CIVIC SCENARIO WORKSHOP, 2000-2001 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 116 - CENTER FOR ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL RIGHTS - KURDISH MINORITY IN IRAN, 2000-2003 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 122 - UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME - ENERGY AND ATMOSPHERE PROGRAMME, 2000-2002 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 123 - HABITAT INTERNATIONAL COALITION (SWITZERLAND) - HUMAN RIGHTS IN TRADE AND INVESTMENT, 2000-2005 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 125 - ESSENTIAL INFORMATION - IPR AND TRANSPARENCY AND ACCOUNTABILITY, 2000-2002 (Box R3781)
    - 2000 GI 127 - BENTON FOUNDATION - ONE WORLD US AND WOMEN AND REPRODUCTIVE RIGHTS, 2000-2002 (Box R3781)
  - Global Philanthropy (GP), AC.2006.029.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 GP 003 - GRADUATE SCHOOL AND UNIVERSITY CENTER OF THE CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - INTERNATIONAL FELLOWS PROGRAM, 1994-2001; 2 folders. (Box R3781)
    - 2000 GP 005 - PENINSULA COMMUNITY FOUNDATION - PHILANTHROPIC INCUBATOR PROJECT, 2000-2004 (Box R3781)
    - 2000 GP 006 - NONPROFIT ENTERPRISE AND SELF-SUSTAINABLILITY TEAM (CHILE) - INTERNATIONAL VENTURE PHILANTHROPY FORUM, 2000-2001 (Box R3781)
    - 2000 GP 007 - TIDES CENTER - GIVINGWELL PROJECT, 2000-2001 (Box R3781)
    - 2000 GP 012 - PHILANTHROPIC INITIATIVE - INCREASING GLOBAL PHILANTHROPY, 2000-2002 (Box R3781)
  - Health Equity (HE), AC.2006.029.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 HE 001 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - TB DRUG DISCOVERY AND DEVELOPMENT, 2000-2001 (Box R3781)
    - 2000 HE 003 - UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND - VACCINE AGAINST SHIGELLA AND E. COLI; PEDIATRIC INFECTIONS IN MALI (BALTIMORE), 1999-2003 (Box R3781)
    - 2000 HE 010 - DOCTORS WITHOUT BORDERS- CONFERENCE ON IMPROVING ACCESS TO ESSENTIAL MEDICINES IN EAST AFRICA, 2000-2002 (Box R3781)
    - 2000 HE 013 - ATENEO DE MANILA UNIVERSITY (PHILIPPINES) - FOSTERING PEOPLE-CENTERED PUBLIC HEALTH STRATEGIES, 2000-2001 (Box R3781)
- AC.2006.034: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1995-2005; AC.2006.034; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3782-R3783.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3782-R3783.
  - Health Equity (HE), AC.2006.034.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 HE 018 - UNIVERSITY OF THE WITWATERSRAND (SOUTH AFRICA) - EQUINET REGIONAL MEETING, 2000-2001 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 HE 026 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - INTERNATIONAL SYSTEMS OF HEALTH RESEARCH, 2000-2001 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 HE 028 - CONSUMERS INTERNATIONAL (ENGLAND) - PEOPLE'S HEALTH ASSEMBLY CONFERENCE, 1999-2002 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 HE 029 - CONSUMERS INTERNATIONAL (ENGLAND) - WORKSHOP ON TOBACCO CONSUMPTION AND CONTROL, 2000-2002 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 HE 031 - MEDICAL RESEARCH COUNCIL (SOUTH AFRICA) - COALITION OF TUBERCULOSIS R&D STAKEHOLDERS, 2000-2002 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 HE 033 - (HEALTH EQUITIY) - BC CONFERENCE: TB DRUG FACILITY (Box R3782)
      Scope and Contents note
      Cancelled.
    - 2000 HE 035 - ACTION ON SMOKING AND HEALTH FOUNDATION (THAILAND) - SOUTHEAST ASIA TOBACCO CONTROL ALLIANCE, 2000-2004 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 HE 044 - MEDICAL RESEARCH COUNCIL (SOUTH AFRICA) - LATIN AMERICA MEETING OF TB STAKEHOLDERS, 2000-2002 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 HE 046 - GLOBAL HEALTH COUNCIL - UNITED NATIONS SPECIAL SESSION FOR CHILDREN, 2000-2002 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 HE 051 - KENYA - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - DISEASE SURVEILLANCE NETWORK, 2000-2005 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 HE 054 - UNIVERSITIY OF CHICAGO - APICOMPLEXAN PARASITES AND NEW MEDICINES, 2000-2002 (Box R3782)
  - Population and Cairo Agenda (PC), AC.2006.034.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2000 PC 003 - ATENEO DE DAVAO UNIVERSITY (PHILIPPINES) - EFFECT OF IMPROVED FAMILY PLANNING AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH SERVICES ON WOMEN, 1997-2003 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 PC 006 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - CHILD MORTALITY AND FERTILITY RATES IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1995-2003 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 PC 008 - TIDES CENTER - IMPLICATIONS OF HEALTH SECTOR REFORMS IN INDIA AND TANZANIA FOR REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 1999-2002 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 PC 015 - DANISH FAMILY PLANNING ASSOCIATION (DENMARK) - EDUCATE FOREIGN ASSISTANCE POLICYMAKERS AND PARLIAMENTARIANS, 1997-2002 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 PC 027 - CENTER FOR HEALTH AND SOCIAL POLICY - ADVANCI NG REPRODUCTIVE AND SEXUAL HEALTH AND RIGHTS, 2000-2002 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 PC 031 - WOMEN'S FUNDING NETWORK - WOMEN'S LENS/CONSTITUENCY BUILDING, 1999-2002 (Box R3782)
    - 2000 PC 032 - ASPEN INSTITUTE - WOMEN'S LENS ON GLOBAL ISSUES, 1998-2003 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 PC 033 - (POPULATION AND CAIRO AGENDA) - GLOBAL GOVERNANCE, 2000-2001 (Box R3783)
  - Program Venture Experiment (PV), AC.2006.034.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 PV 002 - (GLOBAL INCOME INEQUALITIES), 2000-2001 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 PV 009 - ASIA SOCIETY - U.S./INDIA ROUNDTABLE PROJECT, 2000-2002 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 PV 010 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - PARTNERSHIP TO CUT HUNGER IN AFRICA, 2000-2002 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 PV 012 - UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME - MEETING AT POCANTICO RE HUMAN DEVELOPMENT REPORT 2001, 2000-2003 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 PV 013 - (SPECIAL PROGRAMS) - INDEPENDENT COMMISSION ON HUMAN SECURITY, 2000-2004 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 PV 015 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - ASIAN FOOD SYMPOSIUM, 2000-2001 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 PV 016 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - INTERACADEMY COUNCIL, 2000-2002 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 PV 018 - UNIVERSITY OF CAMBRIDGE (ENGLAND) - LIBRARY EXPANSION PROJECT, 2000-2001 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 PV 020 - NEW RENAISSANCE GROUP (ENGLAND) - WORKSHOP ON BOOK, "WHERE NEXT? REFLECTIONS ON THE HUMAN FUTURE", 2000-2002 (Box R3783)
  - Regional Nairobi (RN), AC.2006.034.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 RN 001 - (REGIONAL NAIROBI) - MEETINGS ON PARTNERSHIP FOR AFRICAN RENEWAL, 1999-2002 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 RN 009 - (REGIONAL NAIROBI) - UGANDA COUNTRY PROGRAM, 1999-2003 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 RN 010 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - HUMAN RESOURCES AND DECENTRALIZATION IN UGANDA, 2000-2002 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 RN 012 - WOMEN'S LAW AND PUBLIC POLICY FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM - LEADERSHIP AND ADVOCACY FOR WOMEN IN AFRICA, 2000-2002 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 RN 014 - UNITED NATIONS CENTRE FOR HUMAN SETTLEMENTS (KENYA) - CAMPAIGN ON URBAN GOVERNANCE, 2000-2002 (Box R3783)
    - 2000 RN 015 - ASSOCIATION OF AFRICAN UNIVERSITIES (GHANA) - VARIANTS OF UNIVERSITY EDUCATION, 2000-2002 (Box R3783)
- AC.2006.036: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2005; AC.2006.036; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3784-R3788.; 5 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3784-R3788.
  - Regional Nairobi (RN), AC.2006.036.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 RN 018 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL ON SOCIAL WELFARE (UGANDA) - PARTICIPANTS IN CONFERENCE ON SOCIAL WELFARE, 2000-2003 (Box R3784)
    - 2000 RN 024 - ORGANIZATION FOR SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH IN EASTERN AND SOUTHERN AFRICA (ETHIOPIA) - CONFERENCE ON AFRICAN CONFLICTS, 2000-2002 (Box R3784)
    - 2000 RN 026 - SALZBURG SEMINAR - WORKSHOP ON HIGHER EDUCATION IN EMERGING ECONOMIES, 2000-2002 (Box R3784)
  - RO, AC.2006.036.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 RO 004 - BANGLADESH RURAL ADVANCEMENT COMMITTEE - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2000-2003 (Box R3784)
  - Working Communities (WC), AC.2006.036.3; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - 2000 WC 001 - INTERNATIONAL HUMAN RIGHTS LAW GROUP - BC CONFERENCE: CONSULTATION ON THE WORLD CONFERENCE AGAINST RACISM, 1998-2002 (Box R3784)
    - 2000 WC 002 - INSTITUTE FOR PUBLIC POLICY RESEARCH (ENGLAND) - BC CONFERENCE: PROGRESSIVE GOVERNMENT: COMING TO TERMS WITH THE GLOBAL KNOWLEDGE SOCIETY, 1999-2003 (Box R3784)
    - 2000 WC 003 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - INTERNET-BASED MATCHING SERVICE, 2000-2001 (Box R3784)
    - 2000 WC 004 - COMMUNITY RESOURCE EXCHANGE - HIGHER EDUCATION AND COMMUNITY PARTNERSHIPS, 2000-2001 (Box R3784)
    - 2000 WC 007 - TULANE UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT-DRIVEN COMMUNITY SERVICE PROJECTS, 2000-2001 (Box R3784)
    - 2000 WC 011 - CHAPIN HALL CENTER FOR CHILDREN - POWER AND RACE IN COMMUNITY CHANGE INITIATIVES, 1996-2004 (Box R3784)
    - 2000 WC 012 - HOSTOS COMMUNITY COLLEGE - ENHANCE INSTITUTIONAL CAPACITY, 2000-2004 (Box R3784)
    - 2000 WC 013 - OMEGA BOYS CLUB OF SAN FRANCISCO - "STREET SOLDIERS" RADIO PROGRAM, 1995-2002 (Box R3784)
    - 2000 WC 014 - CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY - COLLABORATIVE TO ENHANCE THE COUNTY'S IMPLEMENTATION OF EMPLOYMENT-RELATED POLICIES, 1999-2003 (Box R3784)
    - 2000 WC 016 - LOUGHBOROUGH UNIVERSITY (ENGLAND) - EXAMINE HOW BRITISH WELFARE REFORM CAN INFORM THE U.S., 2000-2004 (Box R3784)
    - 2000 WC 021 - NEW HOPE PROJECT, INC. - TEST PROGRAMS DESIGNED TO MAKE WORK PAY, 1991-2002; 3 folders. (Box R3785)
    - 2000 WC 024 - COMMUNITY PARTNERS - COMMUNITY JUSTICE RESOURCE CENTER (ADVANCEMEBT PROJECT), 1999-2003 (Box R3785)
    - 2000 WC 027 - UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS - PARTNERSHIP BETWEEN COMMUNITIES AND HIGHER EDUCATION INSTITUTIONS, 2000-2003 (Box R3785)
    - 2000 WC 028 - DEPAUL UNIVERSITY - ASSESS DIVERSITY AMONG TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE PROVIDERS, 2000-2003 (Box R3785)
    - 2000 WC 038 - HUMAN SERVICES ALLIANCES - SUBSIDIZED CHILD CARE ADVOCACY, 2000-2004 (Box R3785)
    - 2000 WC 039 - AFL-CIO CENTER FOR WORKING CAPITAL - GLOBAL PENSION DATABASE, 1999-2002 (Box R3785)
    - 2000 WC 040 - CLF SERVICES - DEMOCRATIC INVESTING, 2000-2002 (Box R3785)
    - 2000 WC 045 - INSTITUTE FOR WISCONSIN'S FUTURE, INC. - MILWAUKEE PARENT ACTION COORDINATION AND TRAINING PROJECT, 2000-2003 (Box R3785)
    - 2000 WC 046 - CENTER FOR LAW AND EDUCATION - THEORIES OF CHANGE IN SCHOOL REFORM, 2000-2004 (Box R3786)
    - 2000 WC 047 - DC AGENDA SUPPORT CORPORATION - COMMUNITY/UNIVERSITY PARTNERSHIP AND RESIDENT'S LEADERSHIP CAPACITY, 2000-2001 (Box R3786)
    - 2000 WC 048 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL - CORE SUPPORT, 1995-2004 (Box R3786)
    - 2000 WC 049 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL - NATIONAL COMMUNITY BUILDING SUPPORT CENTER, 1993-2004; 3 folders. (Box R3786)
    - 2000 WC 049 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL - NATIONAL COMMUNITY BUILDING SUPPORT CENTER - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-2004 (Box R3786)
    - 2000 WC 052 - SAN ANTONIO INDEPENDENT SCHOOL DISTRICT - BUILDING AN INFRASTRUCTURE FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 1994-2002 (Box R3787)
    - 2000 WC 057 - CITYSKILLS - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2000-2005 (Box R3787)
    - 2000 WC 058 - OPNET - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2000-2001 (Box R3787)
    - 2000 WC 065 - COMMUNITY RENEWAL SOCIETY - THE CHICAGO REPORTER, 1996-2002 (Box R3787)
    - 2000 WC 072 - CORPORATION FOR THE ADVANCEMENT OF POLICY EVALUATION - FOR-PROFIT LABOR MARKET INTERMEDIARIES, 2000-2002 (Box R3787)
    - 2000 WC 073 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - CAMPBELL COLLABORATION AND SOCIAL AND EDUCATIONAL INTERVENTIONS, 2000-2004 (Box R3787)
    - 2000 WC 095 - JOBS WITH JUSTICE EDUCATION FUND - SUSTAINABLE GROWTH PROJECT, 2000-2005 (Box R3787)
    - 2000 WC 104 - FISCAL POLICY INSTITUTE - WELFARE AND WORKFARE ISSUES, 2000-2004 (Box R3787)
    - 2000 WC 107 - INTERNATIONAL LABOUR ORGANISATION (SWITZERLAND) - SOCIO-ECONOMIC SECURITY SURVEY; RESEARCH WORKSHOP AND CONFERENCE, 2000-2003 (Box R3787)
    - 2000 WC 115 - CHICAGO JOBS COUNCIL - WORKFUND INITIATIVE, 1999-2002 (Box R3787)
    - 2000 WC 117 - UPRISING COMMUNITY PLUS - COMMUNITY- CONTROLLED CREDIT UNION, 2000-2005 (Box R3787)
    - 2000 WC 119 - FUND FOR THE CITY OF NEW YORK - UNITED STATES-UNITED KINGDOM YOUTH JUSTICE EXCHANGE, 2000-2003 (Box R3788)
    - 2000 WC 121 - (WORKING COMMUNITIES) - REVIEWS OF NEWSPAPER COVERAGE ON WELFARE REFORM AND WORKFORCE DEVELOPMENT, 2000-2001 (Box R3788)
    - 2000 WC 122 - JOBS FOR THE FUTURE - COMMUNICATION/DISSEMINATION ACTIVITIES RELATED TO CONFERENCE, "LOW WAGE WORKERS IN THE NEW ECONOMY", 2000-2003 (Box R3788)
    - 2000 WC 125 - INITIATIVE FOR A COMPETITIVE INNER CITY - CASE STUDY ON MILLWORKS LEARNING AND DEVELOPMENT CENTER, 2000-2002 (Box R3788)
    - 2000 WC 127 - CENTER FOR LAW AND SOCIAL POLICY - TECHNICAL SUPPORT TO LOCAL OFFICIALS FOR TANF RECIPIENTS, 2000-2003 (Box R3788)
    - 2000 WC 130 - NATIONAL BUREAU OF ECONOMIC RESEARCH - EMPLOYEE STOCK OWNERSHIP AND OPTION PLANS IMPACT (Box R3788)
    - 2000 WC 131 - BRANDEIS UNIVERSITY - LOW-SKILLED FEMALE WORKERS RESEARCH PROJECT, 2000-2002 (Box R3788)
    - 2000 WC 134 - (WORKING COMMUNITIES) - CONFERENCE ON WORK AND HEALTH, 2001-2002 (Box R3788)
    - 2000 WC 136 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORPORATION - CONFERENCE ON WELFARE AND WORKFORCE DEVELOPMENT POLICY REFORM, 2000-2001 (Box R3788)
  - Africa Regional (AR), AC.2006.036.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 AR 011 - WAGOIRE, WILLIAM WAMALA - ACA: WHEAT PRODUCTION TECHNOLOGY IN UGANDA, 2000-2003 (Box R3788)
    - 2001 AR 017 - HANOI SCHOOL OF PUBLIC HEALTH (VIETNAM) - WORKSHOP ON SEXUAL MATURATION (Box R3788)
    - 2001 AR 019 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - CHILDREN'S PHOTOGRAPHY PROJECT, 2001-2002 (Box R3788)
    - 2001 AR 020 - MALIAN ASSOCIATION FOR THE SUPPORT OF GIRLS' EDUCATION - FAWE MALI CHAPTER, 2000-2002 (Box R3788)
    - 2001 AR 021 - INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT RESEARCH CENTRE (CANADA) - WORKSHOP FOR GRANTEE INSTITUTIONS IN AFRICA, 2001-2002 (Box R3788)
    - 2001 AR 038 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - QUEST DIALOGUE WITH PRIVATE AND PUBLIC SECTORS, 2001-2002 (Box R3788)
    - 2001 AR 041 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - WORKSHOP FOR PHSWOW AND FORUM STUDENTS (Box R3788)
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC.2006.036.5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 CC 002 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN-MILWAUKEE - ACTIVITIES OF CONSORTIUM OF HUMANITIES CENTERS AND INSTITUTES, 1997-2002 (Box R3788)
    - 2001 CC 003 - WHITNEY MUSEUM OF AMERICAN ART - "DATA DYNAMICS" EXHIBITION AND MEDIA ART THINK TANK CONFERENCE, 2000-2004 (Box R3788)
    - 2001 CC 010 - SIGNATURE THEATRE CO. - PRODUCTION DESIGNER SOFTWARE FOR "URBAN ZULU MAMBO" (Box R3788)
    - 2001 CC 027 - KEAN UNIVERSITY - TRANSLATION/EDITING ARTICLES ON INFECTIOUS DISEASES IN LATIN AMERICA, 1999-2005 (Box R3788)
    - 2001 CC 036 - NEW YORK THEATRE WORKSHOP - PRODUCTION OF UNIVERSES' "SLANGUAGE" (Box R3788)
- AC.2006.039: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1998-2004; AC.2006.039; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3789-R3790.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3789-R3790.
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC.2006.039.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 CC 055 - AL-URDUN AL-JADID RESEARCH CENTER (JORDAN) - "ELITES IN THE MIDDLE EAST" Project, 1999-2002 (Box R3789)
    - 2001 CC 057 - BALCH INSTITUTE - EXHIBITION, "AFRICANS IN AMERICA: THE NEW DIASPORA", 2000-2002 (Box R3789)
    - 2001 CC 068 - BEDOYA, ROBERTO - PROJECT ON CULTURAL INDICES, 2000-2004 (Box R3789)
    - 2001 CC 069 - BROOKLYN ACADEMY OF MUSIC - "ARTS IN MULTIMEDIA" WORKS, 2001-2002 (Box R3789)
    - 2001 CC 071 - LINCOLN CENTER FOR THE PERFORMING ARTS - FESTIVAL 'S "AFRICA OUT LOUD" (Box R3789)
    - 2001 CC 086 - CREATIVE TIME - ARTS FESTIVAL, "CREATIVE TIME IN THE ANCHORAGE, 2001"2001 (Box R3789)
    - 2001 CC 102 - ALASKA NATIVE HERITAGE CENTER - EXHIBITION, "FURS, FEATHERS, AND FIBER - COVERING NATIVE ALASKA", 2001-2002 (Box R3789)
    - 2001 CC 201 - RESEARCH AND TECHNOLOGY EXCHANGE GROUP (FRANCE) - AFRICAN MEDIA PARTNERS NETWORK 1998 ACTIVITIES, 1998-2002 (Box R3789)
  - Food Security (FS), AC.2006.039.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2001 FS 008 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - MEETING OF AFRICAN ASSOCIATION FOR BIOLOGICAL NITROGEN FIXATION (Box R3789)
    - 2001 FS 011 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA - PHYSIOLOGICAL GENETICS OF DROUGHT TOLERANCE IN MAIZE, 2001-2002 (Box R3789)
    - 2001 FS 012 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - CEREAL GENOME WORKSHOP, 2001-2002 (Box R3789)
    - 2001 FS 039 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - CONFERENCE ON PLANT VIROLOGY IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2001-2003 (Box R3789)
    - 2001 FS 046 - INTERNATIONAL LIVESTOCK RESEARCH INSTITUTE (KENYA) - INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON SUSTAINABLE CROP-LIVESTOCK PRODUCTION IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2001-2002 (Box R3789)
    - 2001 FS 047 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - STRENGTHENING PROPOSAL, PUBLICATION AND RESEARCH DISSEMINATION SKILLS WORKSHOPS (Box R3789)
    - 2001 FS 049 - (FOOD SECURITY) - ESSENTIAL AGRICULTURAL LIBRARY FOR SIX UNIVERSITIES IN EASTERN AND SOUTHERN AFRICA (Box R3789)
    - 2001 FS 050 - WEST AFRICA RICE DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATION (IVORY COAST) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR THIERRY CADALEN, 1998-2004 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 FS 068 - TEXAS A&M UNIVERSITY - DROUGHT TOLERANCE TRAINING CAPACITY WORKSHOP, 2001-2002 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 FS 077 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY (KENYA) - GENETIC DIVERSITY AND BANANA WEEVIL POPULATIONS, 2001-2002 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 FS 978 - EDUARDO MONDLANE UNIVERSITY (MOZAMBIQUE) - CONFERENCE ON CROP AND PEST MANAGEMENT (Box R3790)
    - 2001 FS 088A - MERICAN SOCIETY FOR MICROBIOLOGY - COLLOQUIUM ON THE SAFETY OF GENETICALLY MODIFIED CROPS, 2001-2002 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 FS 094 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - DEVELOPMENT OF AGRICULTURAL PROGRAMS, 1998-2001 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 FS 103 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES, LOS BANOS - TRAINING WORKSHOP, "MANAGING TECHNOLOGY FROM RESEARCH TO MARKET" (Box R3790)
    - 2001 FS 108 - ZIMBABWE - LANDS AND AGRICULTURE (MINISTRY OF) - INTERNATIONAL FERTILIZER TRAINING PROGRAM, 2001-2002 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 FS 116 - BRAZILIAN AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ENTERPRISE - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR LUIZ J.C.B. CARVALHO, 1996-2002 (Box R3790)
  - Global Inclusion (GI), AC.2006.039.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 GI 002 - COLLEGE UNIVERSITY RESOURCE INSTITUTE - GLOBAL INTERDEPENDENCE INITIATIVE, 2000-2003 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 GI 005 - ALLIANCE OF SMALL ISLAND STATES - WORKSHOP ON BIOSAFETY PROTOCOL, 2000-2001 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 GI 008 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA - WORKSHOP ON IPR AND AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGIES, 2000-2002 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 GI 010 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - BIOTECHNOLOGY POLICY PLANNING, 2000-2004 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 GI 025 - WORLD AFFAIRS COUNCIL ON NORTHERN CALIFORNIA - CONFERENCE ON GLOBALIZATION (Box R3790)
    - 2001 GI 036 - UNITED NATIONS ASSOCIATION OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA - "BUILDING A CONSTITUTENCY FOR THE UN THROUGH EDUCATION" PROGRAM, 2000-2002 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 GI 041 - PARK RIDGE CENTER - CONFERENCE ON GLOBALIZATION ETHICS, 2000-2002 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 GI 051 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR TRADE AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT (SWITZERLAND) - WORKSHOP ON SAFETY AND TRADE IN BIOTECHNOLOGY, 2001-2002 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 GI 054 - INTERNATIONAL PLANT GENETIC RESOURCES INSTITUTE (ITALY) - INTERNATIONAL UNDERTAKING ON PLANT GENETIC RESOURCES, 2001-2002 (Box R3790)
    - 2001 GI 059 - BLACK, STEPHANIE KAREN - DOCUMENTARY FILM "LIFE AND DEBT", 2000-2002 (Box R3790)
- AC.2006.042: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1998-2004; AC.2006.042; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3791-R3792; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3791-R3792.
  - Global Inclusion (GI), AC.2006.042.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 GI 060 - NATIONAL POLICY ASSOCIATION - CONFERENCE ON CORPORATE SOCIAL RESPONSIBILITY AND ROLE OF GOVERNMENT, 2001-2002 (Box R3791)
    - 2001 GI 070 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR THE ACQUISITION OF AGRl-BIOTECH APPLICATIONS - AFRICA BIOTECHNOLOGY WORKSHOP, 2001-2002 (Box R3791)
    - 2001 GI 074 - CRISIS MANAGEMENT INITIATIVE {FINLAND) - WEB PORTAL, 2001-2002 (Box R3791)
    - 2001 GI 079 - (GLOBAL INCLUSION) - IPR AND THE DEVELOPING WORLD (Box R3791)
  - Health Equity (HE), AC.2006.042.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2001 HE 002 - UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE MALAYSIA - TB REGIONAL MEETING, 2000-2004 (Box R3791)
    - 2001 HE 005 - (INITIATIVES FOR EQUITY IN HEALTH) - VOLUME ON GLOBAL DIMENSIONS OF HEALTH EQUITY, 1999-2001 (Box R3791)
    - 2001 HE 005 - (INITIATIVES FOR EQUITY IN HEALTH) - VOLUME ON GLOBAL DIMENSIONS OF HEALTH EQUITY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1999-2001 (Box R3791)
      Separated Materials
      Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
      - [untitled], 2006.042.001; 1 Item(s) CD-R
      - Challening Inequities in Health: From Ethics to Action, 2006.042.002; 1 Item(s) CD-R
      - Challening Inequities in Health: From Ethics to Action, 2006.042.003; 1 Item(s) CD-R
      - GH Book in PDF Files, 2006.042.004; 1 Item(s) CD-R
    - 2001 HE 007 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - TRANSFERRING OF VACCINE PRODUCTION TECHNOLOGY (Box R3791)
    - 2001 HE 014 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - BC CONFERENCE: STOP TB INITIATIVE, 2000-2003 (Box R3791)
    - 2001 HE 021 - SALZBURG SEMINAR - SEMINAR ON PATIENT SAFETY AND MEDICAL ERROR, 2000-2002 (Box R3791)
    - 2001 HE 022 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - DECENTRALIZATION MEETING IN NAIROBI (Box R3791)
    - 2001 HE 031 - WORLDWIDE DOCUMENTARIES - DOCUMENTARY ON AIDS ENTITLED "A CLOSER WALK", 2000-2004 (Box R3791)
    - 2001 HE 037 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE ON EQUITY GOALS OF HEALTH SYSTEMS ON DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2001-2004 (Box R3791)
    - 2001 HE 049 - PROGRAM FOR APPROPRIATE TECHNOLOGY IN HEALTH - MICROBICIDES INITIATIVE, 2001-2002 (Box R3791)
    - 2001 HE 056 - PAN AMERICAN HEALTH ORGANIZATION - EQUITY GAUGE WORKSHOPS IN MEXICO, 2001-2003 (Box R3791)
    - 2001 HE 057 - AIDS EMPOWERMENT AND TREATMENT INTERNATIONAL - DRUG TREATMENT AND SOCIAL SUPPORT, 2001-2003 (Box R3791)
    - 2001 HE 072 - UNIVERSITY OF YORK (UNITED KINGDOM) - INTERNATIONAL HEALTH ECONOMICS ASSOCIATION CONFERENCE, 2001-2003 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 HE 078 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - AFFORDABLE ANTIRETROVIRAL TREATMENT, 2001-2002 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 HE 086 - INFECTIOUS DESEASES SOCIETY OF AMERICA - HIV/AIDS CONFERENCE, 2001-2003 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 HE 103 - FOUNDATION FOR THE NATIONAL INSTITUTES OF HEALTH - THIRD PAN-AFRICAN CONFERENCE ON MALARIA, 2001-2003 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 HE 124 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - INDEPTH AND GLOBAL EQUITY GAUGE ALLIANCE, 2001-2002 (Box R3792)
  - Special Programs (SP), AC.2006.042.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 SP 201 - TUSKEGEE UNIVERSITY - WORKSHOP ON AFRICAN AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPOMENT, 2001-2005 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 SP 204 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - DONATION OF SCULPTURE (Box R3792)
    - 2001 SP 208 - (SPECIAL PROGRAMS) - PURCHASE EMERGENCY SUPPLIES IN RESPONSE TO ATTACKS.ON WORLD TRADE CENTER (Box R3792)
    - 2001 SP 213 - LEWISPORTE MIDDLE SCHOOL (CANADA) - SUPPORT COMPUTER LABORATORY (Box R3792)